RG 002:025, Joint Standing Committee on Agriculture
Connecticut State Library
Joint Standing Committee on Agriculture records
1916-1941, bulk 1940
1940-1941
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. General Assembly. Joint Standing Committee on Agriculture
1 cubic feet
Records from the Committee's study to determine whether the various agricultural departments of the state should be consolidated.
RG002_025_AGR
1948-003
Scope and Content
These records from the study include the following: minutes of meetings February 2, 1940 to May 31, 1940; correspondence with the heads of various state agricultural departments requesting information regarding the departments' personnel, activities, costs of operation, opinions as to whether overlap exists with other departments, and recommendations; correspondence with other states to inquire about how agricultural departments are organized elsewhere; and requests for reumbursement of traveling and other expenses by Committee members.
Related Material
, Connecticut State Library.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Administrative agencies -- Connecticut; Agriculture -- Connecticut; Connecticut. General Assembly. Joint Standing Committee on Agriculture -- Records and correspondence
Document Types:
Correspondence; Invoices; Pamphlets; Purchase orders
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Study to Determine Whether Various Agricultural Departments of the State Should be Consolidated, 1939-1941
  Actual folders are not numbered.
  - Accounting, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Commitment lists, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Invoice lists, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Purchase orders, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dairy & Food Commision, Hon. Edwin G. Woodward, Commissioner, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Domestic Animal Dept., Hon. Ray Harding, Commissioner, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Department of Health, Dr. Stanley H.; Osborn, Commissioner, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Milk Administration, Hon. S. McLean Buckingham, Administrator, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Milk Regulation Board, Hon. Edwin G. Woodward, Chairman, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - University of Connecitcut, Dr. A.N. Jorgensen, President, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - H.B. 1072, S.A. 541, 1939 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Governing board statutory references, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Letter to Agrucultural Department of the State, 1940 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1940 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes, 1940 February 12 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Minutes, 1940 April 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Minutes, 1940 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Commissioners of Agriculture in the United States, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Dept. of Agriculture, Hon. Olcott F. King, Commissioner, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, Dr. WIlliam L. Slate, Director, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Budget Division, Mr. Robert W. Weir, Director, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Albert E. Anthony, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - George H. Augur, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Ernest H. Averill, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Claude V. Badger, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Thomas L. Burgess, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Walter G. Colton, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Henry J. Delay, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - John M. Dooley, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Donald A. Fraser, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Warren L. Hunt, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Julius B. Lewis, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Louis S. Moseley, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Frank H. Peet, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Asa R. Scranton, Jr., 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Cleveland Stannard, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - M. Morgan Strong, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Frank L. White, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Alabama, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Arizona, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Arkansas, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - California, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Colorado, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Connecticut (Box 1, Folder 44)
    This folder is empty.
  - Delaware, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - District of Columbia, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Florida, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Georgia, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Idaho, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Illinois, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Indiana, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Iowa, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Kansas, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Kentucky, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Louisiana, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Maine, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Maryland, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Massachusetts, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Michigan, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Minnesota, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Mississippi, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Missouri, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Montana, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Nebraska, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Nevada, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - New Hampshire, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - New Jersey, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - New Mexico, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - New York, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - North Carolina, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - North Dakota, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Ohio, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Oklahoma, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Oregon, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Pennsylvania, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Rhode Island, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - South Carolina, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - South Dakota, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Tennessee, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Texas, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Utah, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Vermont, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Virginia, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Washington, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - West Virginia, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Wisconsin, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Wyoming, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Miscellaneous, 1916-1940 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    Publications and statutes concerning agriculture from other states.